Guide to the Mark Hall Amitin/ World of Culture for the Performing Arts, Inc. Archive MSS.121
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IX: Printed matter
  - Esquire, Jun 1986 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_5dd81495b060f64865b5b8c7dc9a7596)
  - Fag Rag, Fall, Winter 1973 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_0cff253d10d894c5f5c51a79b627ebe6)
  - Festival Caracas, 1983 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_0be7e3a1feb36269caa66c23dbe428aa)
  - Film Quarterly, Summer 1985 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_812240b97637892c4dba21f9533da816)
  - Hamptons Magazine, Jul 1991-Aug 1993 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_1ebae567f31465bcce360f6c61ef3840)
  - The Hollywood Reporter, 1986-1987 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_6af25973b3e2249041833a3f6c857799)
  - The Hollywood Reporter, Nov 26, 1991 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_fa1bd11451d421aea41e0082fe048b40)
  - Movies USA, Nov 1991 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_906d312f84d013df639e2c52bd23389c)
  - New Books in Theater and Dramatic, undated (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_218890ee2911789e606e1be9dbc6ea81)
  - Studies, 1983 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_b126fa163e9e36a4a97d527a9c5d9f13)
  - New York, Dec 1987 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_f90d465f2c36eea0ea46d304c14d6cfe)
  - Night and Day, May 28, 1990 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_069133c4c1121b66f0af78e3fae21a9f)
  - On Stage New York, Oct 1985 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_5bd8035b2a7f74e36e9ba651965d1965)
  - Premiere, May 1989 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_e4882b24df64168e0c4accbeeaaed039)
  - Soap Opera Weekly, Jun 18, 1991 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_34e1a5b21b880f73c5692dbef55c1211)
  - Theatre Crafts, Oct 1991 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_3dbfe145e19faf8792fcbd9092dca619)
  - Theater: Ex, Spring 1986 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_0319f4f40fbcd275a9dea758dfe35268)
  - Theater Week, Dec 1987 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_fc4cc75e70a711e47fb303a1e9a45258)
  - Theater Week, Jan 1988 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_ea41ba9ec9dbc4ea643e61cab93bf22f)
  - Theater Week, Dec 1990 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_da7f2788ebaa9221402f39b984ec97fb)
  - Time Out, Oct 1991-Nov 1991 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_b0889395d4fcce78deec4531ab388762)
  - TV Guide, Apr 3, 1993-Apr 9, 1993 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_3b7b28653d8db88546c5cd40c40f9262)
  - TV Guide, Mar 13, 1993Mar 19, 1993 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_5604c528644b5c713769ef05a4373107)
  - Vanity Fair, Jan 1984 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_3932289c1906033087a92aa8f9553977)
  - The Westsider, Jul 1993-Sep 1993 (Box 80, Folder data_value_missing_e6e23830a169cae3cad9ebe85593bb0a)